Terrifying Gorgon's Head
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Nobita!
As your punishment, stand outside the classroom!
Yes, sir!
My feet hurts!
What's wrong?
I've sprained my feet.
Do you have a gadget that will protect my feet from getting sprained?
You do nothing and yet your legs get sprained?
I've been forced to stand outside the classroom, but my feet hurts!
So you should ensure that you don't have to stand outside the classroom.
Forget it!
I am confident...
That I will forget to do my homework, again.
And I'll take a nap.
So I ask you, do you have a gadget to protect my feet from getting sprained?
You're so hopeless!
But what's that supposed to be?
It is the Gorgon's head.
It is a very terrifying gadget, so you must be careful when you use it.
It's eyes spurt out beams which can eat your tissues and turn you into a stone.
But I don't want such a gadget!
Don't worry, you just have to be careful!
Really?
Aim at your legs!
I can't move!
I can't move my feet!
Oh, no!
Your feet have became stone.
Since your feet are now stone...
Your feet can't get sprained even if you stand for hours.
You are right!
How great!
If you pull this snake's hood-shaped Gorgon's hair...
You will be back to normal.
You are right.
I will take it to school tomorrow.
Nobita, you forgot to do your homework again!
Stand outside the classroom.
Yes, sir!
How breezy.
Now it feels like I'm sitting on a stone.
That's it!
I can now turn anyone I hate into a stone!
But, no, it's boring.
I should make my hand turn into a stone... and hit Giant...
He would then get dizzy and faint!
How great!
Are you that happy to stand outside the classroom?
Stand here for the rest of today!
Yes, sir!
I'm late to go home!
Oh no! I dropped the Gorgon's Head!
What? You dropped Gorgon's Head!???
I dropped it at the hill behind our school!
It's terrible!
If someone approaches it, they will turn into a stone!
We must capture it at once.
Around here.
But it can move around.
It knows how to move.
But thankfully, its speed is very slow like that of a tortoise.
But how are we going to find and capture it?
We must be careful not to get spotted by it...
Slowly find it and close it with this box.
I hope we could find it ASAP.
Shh!
It's our teacher!
Sir...!
He has turned into a stone.
Don't let your guard down, it should be somewhere around here.
D-Doraemon!
So there it is!
My feet can't move, Doraemon!
Hey! Don't leave me alone!
Doraemon has turned into a stone...
What? Is it that terrifying?
Right.
It will be bad if we can't capture it ASAP.
You'll help me, right?
I can't!
It's your fault, you must capture it by yourself.
But if we can't capture it soon, it will go into your house.
But that'd be a problem!
Nobita, It is your responsibility.
It's your fault for doing weird things!
Leave it to me, I have a good plan.
What?
Don't ask more, follow me and you will know.
Giant, if you go deep into the forest...
The Gorgon will...
Well, I am going to hide here. You two find and lure it here!
What?
Don't wanna!
Nobita!
I'll run ahead of you...!
Suneo, how dare you push me...!
Hurry, run!
Nobita, you captured it all by yourself?
How did you capture that?
It is unimaginable.
Because I let it run away.
So it was my responsibility!